{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Pool Heater Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40370/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40370,"taskName":"Swimming Pool Heaters - Repair or Service","taskDescription":"Repair or Service Swimming Pool Heaters","xmTaskDescriptor":"Pool Heater Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":187,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Pools replacement maintain filter costs","textMessagingName":"Repr Pool Heater","rolloverLongDesc":"Will troubleshoot pool equipment \u0026 handle any necessary maintenance or repairs.","rolloverShortDesc":"Filters, pumps, bubblers, heaters, chlorinators, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Service Swimming Pool Heaters.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Pool Heater Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix a Pool Heater","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":61,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Swimming Pool Heaters Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Swimming Pool Heaters - Repair or Service","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Swimming Pool Heater Project","urlName":"Swimming-Pool-Heaters-Repair-or-Service","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Pool Heater Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Pools,replacement,maintain,filter,costs,care,maintenance,tub,hot,ground,sauna,material,inground,Swimming,Heaters,above,Equipment,semi","emcCategoryOid":-12070,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":664,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40370/":{"taskOID":40370,"originalTaskOID":40370,"setID":664,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4864,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of pool do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3182,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5914,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Spa/hot tub","answerDisplayText":"Spa/hot tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":589,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4865,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Heater","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of heater do you use?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4027,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural gas","answerDisplayText":"Natural gas","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4939,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Propane","answerDisplayText":"Propane","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4340,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oil","answerDisplayText":"Oil","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2168,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Electric immersion","answerDisplayText":"Electric immersion","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2948,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5868,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Solar","answerDisplayText":"Solar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5870,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Solar blanket","answerDisplayText":"Solar blanket","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11530,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4868,"questionDisplayText":"Problems","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need service/repair? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2957,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Heater won't turn on","answerDisplayText":"Heater won't turn on","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4687,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pilot light won't stay lit","answerDisplayText":"Pilot light won't stay lit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2954,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heater leaking","answerDisplayText":"Heater leaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2952,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Heater cycles on and off","answerDisplayText":"Heater cycles on and off","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2956,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Heater won't shut off","answerDisplayText":"Heater won't shut off","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6886,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Water not heating to desired temperature","answerDisplayText":"Water not heating to desired temperature","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4072,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Need regular maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Need regular maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4864,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of pool do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3182,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5914,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Spa/hot tub","answerDisplayText":"Spa/hot tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":589,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3182,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5914,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Spa/hot tub","answerDisplayText":"Spa/hot tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":589,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4865,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Heater","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of heater do you use?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4027,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural gas","answerDisplayText":"Natural gas","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4939,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Propane","answerDisplayText":"Propane","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4340,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oil","answerDisplayText":"Oil","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2168,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Electric immersion","answerDisplayText":"Electric immersion","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2948,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5868,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Solar","answerDisplayText":"Solar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5870,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Solar blanket","answerDisplayText":"Solar blanket","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11530,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4027,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural gas","answerDisplayText":"Natural gas","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4939,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Propane","answerDisplayText":"Propane","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4340,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oil","answerDisplayText":"Oil","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2168,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Electric immersion","answerDisplayText":"Electric immersion","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2948,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5868,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Solar","answerDisplayText":"Solar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5870,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Solar blanket","answerDisplayText":"Solar blanket","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11530,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4868,"questionDisplayText":"Problems","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need service/repair? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2957,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Heater won't turn on","answerDisplayText":"Heater won't turn on","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4687,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pilot light won't stay lit","answerDisplayText":"Pilot light won't stay lit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2954,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heater leaking","answerDisplayText":"Heater leaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2952,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Heater cycles on and off","answerDisplayText":"Heater cycles on and off","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2956,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Heater won't shut off","answerDisplayText":"Heater won't shut off","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6886,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Water not heating to desired temperature","answerDisplayText":"Water not heating to desired temperature","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4072,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Need regular maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Need regular maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2957,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Heater won't turn on","answerDisplayText":"Heater won't turn on","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4687,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pilot light won't stay lit","answerDisplayText":"Pilot light won't stay lit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2954,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heater leaking","answerDisplayText":"Heater leaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2952,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Heater cycles on and off","answerDisplayText":"Heater cycles on and off","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2956,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Heater won't shut off","answerDisplayText":"Heater won't shut off","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6886,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Water not heating to desired temperature","answerDisplayText":"Water not heating to desired temperature","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4072,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Need regular maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Need regular maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}